PATRICIO EDUARDO CORDERO ESPEJO

patricio@espejozen.cl

+56 9 7617 3243

I am a Software Engineer with more than 10 years of experience performing roles as Web Developer, Project Manager, IT Support Coordinator and Fullstack Software Engineer, in companies of different areas, such as Industry, Engineering and Health.

I always seek to grow and generates changes that add value to the projects in which I participate. I believe that the basis of success is in teamwork, empathy, responsibility, and talent that each member can contribute to common goals. I believe in good leadership, which generates commitment and results, being part of the team, as well as guides and mentors of potential talents and personal growth

SKILLS

Programming Languages C#, PHP, Javascript, Python

Frontend Stack HTML5, CSS3, SASS, ASP .NET, WebForms, Angular 4+,

ReactJS, jQuery, AngularJS, NextJS

Backend Stack .NET Framework 4.5+, .NET Core, Entity Framework,

NodeJS, ExpressJS, API, DDD, REST, SOAP, JWT Auth

Mobile Stack Flutter, React Native

Databases SQL Server 2014+, MySQL, MongoDB

Infrastructure Cloud Providers:

Azure, AWS, DigitalOcean, Linode

OS:

Ubuntu, Debian, CentOS, Windows Server 2012+

Technologies:

IIS, Apache, Nginx, Docker, Kubernetes, Docker Compose

CI/CD:

Azure Pipelines, Bitbucket Pipelines

Others GIT, Azure Devops, Jira, Slack, MS Teams

EXPERIENCE

easycancha (RODA SPA)

Feb 2021-Now

Fullstack Software Engineer

Development of new features, frontend, backend, infrastructure and mobile

- Get user metadata info (App React Native)
- New booking flow
- Ads Product from partners
- BI python routines, implementation and maintaining
- Automatic deployment using Bitbucket Pipelines, to a beta (AWS EC2 and docker instance) and a production (AWS EKS Kubernetes cluster) environment
- Improve MySQL Pools behavior
- Webpay Transbank Mall REST integration
- Subscription model implementation (frontend, backend, and BI implementations)
- CLI creation for batch operations, like db dump sync, db tables population, and others
- CDN implementation using AWS S2 and AWS CloudFront

Tecnigen S.A.

Nov 2017-Feb 2021

Fullstack Software Engineer

Development of web and desktop apps. Integration of HIS and LIS systems, for health companies related.

- Critical Values of Laboratory Exams Monitor
- Laboratory Derivated Exams Tracking System
- Health Statistics Module (PowerBI Integration)
- Authentication and autorization module
- Base architecture for API (C#, NetCORE, DDD, Repository Pattern, DI Pattern, and others)
- Technical Assistant Mobile App (Flutter, integration with on-premise ERP systems)
- Technical advisor in CAB (Change Advisory Board)

IQS S.A.

Jun 2016-Nov 2017

Fullstack Engineer

Api and web development for industry companies related like Arauco and CMPC

- OHSAS Cloud (API, Angular 2)
- Relay Race 2 (API, Angular2)
- Relay Race (API, AngularJS)
- Doctor Cloud (API, IS3, NodeJS, ExpressJS, Socket.io, Angular 4+)

Derecho a Saber Ltda.

Sep 2013-May 2016

Web Developer

- SISQUIM (Chemical Information System)
- MINIMIZA (Industrial waste management system)

- DAS

IT Support Coordinator

- Linux servers support (Debian, Ubuntu)
- Equipment adquisition, technical advicing
- Problems resolution

IT Support

- Workstation support
- Webapp development

Mandril Digital SPA

Web Developer

Nov 2012-Sep 2013

- Webapp development
- Emailing webapp, Mailchimp service integration
- ERP Web

Aeurus Ltda.

Project Manager

Oct 2011-Nov 2012

- Project leadership
- Management of customer requirements
- Software design and analysis
- Planning and control

Web Developer

- Website development
- Ecommerce

EDUCATION

I. Prof. Virginio Gomez

2010-2015

Ingeniería en Computación e Informática

OTHER KNOWLEDGES

Languages Spanish (Native)

English (read and write, uncompleted B1 conversational

course)

PERSONAL INFO

Birthday November 16, 1982

Country Chile

Hobbies Music (Sing, Guitar, Ukelele), Soccer